<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code on Jade Meskill</title>
    <link>/categories/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code on Jade Meskill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 17:31:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue/Green Deploys with Kubernetes and Amazon ELB</title>
      <link>/2015/06/13/bluegreen-deploys-with-kubernetes-and-amazon-elb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/13/bluegreen-deploys-with-kubernetes-and-amazon-elb/</guid>
      <description>At Octoblu, we deploy very frequently and we&amp;#8217;re tired of our users seeing the occasional blip when a new version is put into production.
Though we&amp;#8217;re using Amazon Opsworks to more easily manage our infrastructure, our updates can take a while for dependencies to be installed before the service restarts &amp;#8211; not a great experience.
Enter Kubernetes. We knew that moving to an immutable infrastructure approach would help us deploy our apps, which range from extremely simple web services, to complex near-real-time messaging systems, quicker and easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes Connect: Invalid Binary</title>
      <link>/2010/08/10/itunes-connect-invalid-binary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 05:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/08/10/itunes-connect-invalid-binary/</guid>
      <description>Invalid Binary.
Gee thanks Apple for that insightful, descriptive message. Surely with all your advanced binary scanning, static analysis, Application Uploader, etc. all you can give us is a most unhelpful &amp;#8220;Invalid Binary&amp;#8221;?
If you are suffering from &amp;#8220;Invalid Binary&amp;#8221; issues, and have done everything short of sacrificing small farm animals, try this trick.
If your Entitlements.plist file was generated with an version of Xcode prior Xcode 3.2.3, remove Entitlements.plist and regenerate it using Xcode 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Build iPhone 3.0 and iOS4 Apps On The Same Machine</title>
      <link>/2010/06/15/how-to-build-iphone-3-0-and-ios4-apps-on-the-same-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 05:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/06/15/how-to-build-iphone-3-0-and-ios4-apps-on-the-same-machine/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s actually really easy, here&amp;#8217;s how I&amp;#8217;ve set it up:
Install the XCode 3.2.3 with iOS4 in /Developer
Install XCode 3.2.2 with iPhone OS 3.2 in /Developer322
Install latest XCode 4.0 developer preview in /DeveloperBeta
This makes it trivially easy to support the older SDKs and toolsets for handling your legacy iPhone applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brave New World</title>
      <link>/2010/04/25/a-brave-new-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 19:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/04/25/a-brave-new-world/</guid>
      <description>No, not a [amazon ASIN=&amp;#8221;0060850523&amp;#8243;]dystopian novel about eugenics[/amazon], this is my re-attempt to commit to a blogging world.
Hello all faithful followers (yes, Mom, I&amp;#8217;m talking to you). Today is a new day, a new dawn, a fresh start, what have you. I have decided that I need to make a new commitment to blogging. I need to force myself to practice and dramatically improve my writing and communication skills. I had previously maintained a blog over at http://iamruinous.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>