<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>agile on Jade Meskill</title>
    <link>/tags/agile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in agile on Jade Meskill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 15:25:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/agile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Twenty-Something Theses of Autonomy</title>
      <link>/2014/01/27/twenty-something-theses-of-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/01/27/twenty-something-theses-of-autonomy/</guid>
      <description>I believe in a radically different organization than what exists in the world today. In order to build the new economy (and thus a new world) our ideas of how an organization works must be challenged (“You can’t make an omelete [sic] without nuking the existing social order“). A keystone of this “new way” is Autonomy. In order to get the best results, Freedom is essential. I have begun the process of capturing my theory in my “Twenty-Something Theses of Autonomy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Coaching / Facilitation Toolkit</title>
      <link>/2012/04/24/my-coaching-facilitation-toolkit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 01:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/04/24/my-coaching-facilitation-toolkit/</guid>
      <description>I was asked recently to document what’s I use for my toolkit when I’m at a client engagement. I’ve experimented with many different options and materials over the last year and so I’ll share with you what I’m currently using.
Before I show you the list, I want to share my philosophy that your toolkit needs to be simple, yet flexible. You never know what might happen during the course of a meeting you are facilitating, therefore you need to be prepared for anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I became a Certified ScrumMaster</title>
      <link>/2010/11/24/why-i-became-a-certified-scrummaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 06:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/11/24/why-i-became-a-certified-scrummaster/</guid>
      <description>On November 22nd I officially became a Certified ScrumMaster(CSM). I went to my CSM training with Michael Vizdos. I was surprised at what I was able to learn, and the level of conversation was much higher than I had anticipated. To put things in context, we have been using Scrum at Integrum for over 4 years, we have had multiple other CSMs and a CSP on staff, so I figured that I’d heard it all before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>