<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Jade Meskill</title>
    <link>/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Jade Meskill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 04:52:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gangplank on Arizona Horizon</title>
      <link>/2013/09/13/gangplank-on-arizona-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 04:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/09/13/gangplank-on-arizona-horizon/</guid>
      <description>I appeared on Arizona Horizon on PBS on Wednesday. You can watch the video here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking The Future of Humanity at TEDxLivermore</title>
      <link>/2013/09/12/hacking-the-future-of-humanity-at-tedxlivermore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 05:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/09/12/hacking-the-future-of-humanity-at-tedxlivermore/</guid>
      <description>On June 8th, 2013 I spoke at TEDxLivermore about Hacking the Future of Humanity. The videos were recently published and now you can watch it for yourself.
  From the Youtube Video:
 Jade Meskill believes we have a choice: we can continue to condemn our children to a life of mediocrity through our apathy….or we can deliver them a future made of magnificence. Delving into the true hacker ethic, Jade poses the question: “How do you hack the system to leave our kids a magnificent future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch – A Crucial Coaching Technique</title>
      <link>/2012/04/23/lunch-a-crucial-coaching-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 18:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/04/23/lunch-a-crucial-coaching-technique/</guid>
      <description>Make time to go to lunch with the people you are serving.
I’ve learned far more about the organization, the people I’m working with, and the challenges that lie ahead by going to lunch with someone almost every single day I’m on site.
I believe that lunch is one of the least respected and valued times in American culture. It is a critical time of day to step back and release from the focus of our daily work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not To Have A Fierce Conversation</title>
      <link>/2011/06/16/how-not-to-have-a-fierce-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 03:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2011/06/16/how-not-to-have-a-fierce-conversation/</guid>
      <description>I have been reading the book [amazon ASIN=”038552904X”]Fierce Conversations[/amazon]. It has helped me to have a much more direct approach to difficult conversations, especially the ones that you really want to put off because they are so uncomfortable.
Recently at Integrum we have been undergoing a lot of deep, radical change, more about that in a later post. This has required me to have some very honest conversations with my entire team, much of it unpleasant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brave New World</title>
      <link>/2010/04/25/a-brave-new-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 19:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/04/25/a-brave-new-world/</guid>
      <description>No, not a [amazon ASIN=”0060850523″]dystopian novel about eugenics[/amazon], this is my re-attempt to commit to a blogging world.
Hello all faithful followers (yes, Mom, I’m talking to you). Today is a new day, a new dawn, a fresh start, what have you. I have decided that I need to make a new commitment to blogging. I need to force myself to practice and dramatically improve my writing and communication skills. I had previously maintained a blog over at http://iamruinous.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>